const dayEighteenQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Who is the carpenter among prophets?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Zakariyah",
      "Prophet Salih",
      "Prophet Lut",
      "Prophet Daud",
      "Prophet Nuh",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Allah gave a prophet of Israil a sonorous voice that He did not give anybody else except him, what is the name of the prophet?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Dhul Kifl",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Daud",
      "Prophet Harun",
      "Prophet ‘Issa",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Allah sent two Angels to Babylon, where magic was prevalent; to teach them and advise them that magic is not good for them, what are the names of the two Angels?",
    options: [
      "Haabil and Qaabil",
      "Harut and Marut",
      "Raqib and ‘Atid",
      "Jinn and Jaan",
      "Israfil and Mikail",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the prophet sent to the people of Thamud?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Hud",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Salih",
      "Prophet Shu’aib",
      "Prophet Lut",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How old was Prophet Adam before his death?",
    options: [
      "950 years",
      "990 years",
      "995 years",
      "1000 years",
      "1001 years",
    ],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A prophet of Allah instructed his child to know and believe two things; Lailah illa lah and Subhanah llah, and as well forbids for his child two things; Shirk and Kibr (Polytheism and Arrogance), what is the name of the prophet?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Zakariyah",
      "Prophet Salih",
      "Prophet Lut",
      "Prophet Daud",
      "Prophet Nuh",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the prophet sent to the people of first ‘Ad’?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Hud",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Salih",
      "Prophet Shu’aib",
      "Prophet Lut",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of gang leader that killed the camel among the people of Prophet Salih (May the peace of Allaah be upon him)?",
    options: [
      "‘Amru bn ‘Aamir bn Luhayi Al Khuza’iy",
      "Quddaru bn Salifi bn Junda’I",
      "Luhluati Almajusiy",
      "Namrud",
      "Wahsha bn Uba",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Prophet Isma’eel’s mother?",
    options: ["Hannah", "‘Asiyah", "Sarah", "Hajarah", "Hawa"],
    correctOption: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "On what day of the month did the drowning of Fir’aun and his soldiers occur?",
    options: [
      "Laylatul Qadr",
      "‘Ashura",
      "Nisfus Sha’ban",
      "Yamul ‘Arafa",
      "Yaomul ‘Eid",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Fir’aun, Haamana and their soldiers were drowned. Who subsided among people of Prophet Musa?",
    options: ["Jalut", "Talut", "Qaarun", "Yusha’u", "Satilu"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many years are in between the construction of Ka’bah and Baitul Maqdis (Jerusalem Mosque)?",
    options: ["1 year", "10 years", "20 years", "30 years", "40 years"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Prophet Musa travelled to learn from a Prophet, what is the name of the Prophet?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Dhul Kifl",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Hadir",
      "Prophet Harun",
      "Prophet Idris",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of a prophet that was buried by companions of Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) during the regime of Umar bn Khatab (May Allaah be pleased with him)?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Dhul Kifl",
      "Prophet Ilyasa’",
      "Prophet Daniyal",
      "Prophet Hadir",
      "Prophet Harun",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "During Israh wal mihraj, Prophet Muhammad (May the peace and blessing of Allaah be upon him) passed by a prophet praying inside his grave beside red sand hill. What is the name of this prophet?",
    options: [
      "Prophet Isma’eel",
      "Prophet Musa",
      "Prophet Ibraheem",
      "Prophet Lut",
      "Prophet Ayub",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];

export default dayEighteenQuestions;
